https://www.bluerockstation.com/privacy-policy-2/

Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
When you send a contact us form, we will capture your e-mail address for our internal mailing list.  If you wish to be removed from this list, you can indicate “Remove” and you will be deleted from the database.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.  We do not share your data with any third-party marketing companies.
Download book for free…
The unvarnished past, present and future of energy, from 1492 to today.
Learn how early innovations in energy came largely due to man’s pursuit of beer. How Benjamin Franklin nearly killed himself electrocuting turkeys. How an Italian scientist believed he discovered the human soul while making frog leg soup for his girlfriend – which ultimately lead to the invention of the battery. And much, much more
Sustainability Menu • Earthship Tours
• Upcoming Classes
• Cool Buildings
• Green Living Books
• Internships
• About Blue Rock Station
• Directions
• Speaking/Consulting
• School Trips
• Workshop FAQs
• Free School
• Our Solar Array
• Our Podcasts
Solar PV Textbooks Available Dozens of colleges and technical schools across the nation use our textbooks to train the next generation of solar installers/designers.
Understanding Photovoltaics takes students from ground zero to having the skills to design and install residential-scale solar electric system.
Designing & Installing Solar PV Systems builds upon the beginning text, expanding on the design of PV systems, dealing with project management and finances, and exploring commercial PV systems.
Free teaching material (lab projects, videos, PowerPoints, curriculum and more) are available to instructors who wish to use the text in class.
Recent Posts
39 Years and Counting…
An Almost Unbelievable Story
How about something positive for a change?
Solar Generator Class Held in Columbus, Helps Asylum Seeker
Pregnant Goats Hiding From Hunters – News from Blue Rock Station
